Guide to the Jane Sumner Accessions
The Wittliff Collections
Jane Sumner Accessions
1973-2015
The Wittliff Collections https://www.thewittliffcollections.txstate.edu
Sumner, Jane
UPWC.15107
9 Linear Feet
9 boxes
Sumner's literary papers detail the many topics she reported on during her career, cairca 1973-2015, which paralleled the rise of a viable Texas film industry. Included are college writings, newspapers with published articles, VHS tapes, microcassette tapes, interview cassette tapes (with subjects such as Bill Wittliff, Richard Linklater, Robert Duvall, Sissy Spacek, etc.), original drafts, and interview transcripts. The folder titles preceding a colon reflect Sumner's original description.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Jane Sumner, 2015
Biographical Note
Jane Sumner is an award-winning journalist best known for her film writing in the pages of the Dallas Morning News.
Scope and Contents
Sumner's literary papers detail the many topics she reported on during her career, circa 1973-2015, which paralleled the rise of a viable Texas film industry. Included are college writings, newspapers with published articles, VHS tapes, microcassette tapes, interview cassette tapes (with subjects such as Bill Wittliff, Richard Linklater, Robert Duvall, Sissy Spacek, etc.), original drafts, and interview transcripts. The folder titles preceding a colon reflect Sumner's original description.
Index Terms
Subjects
Film critics -- United States; Actors -- United States -- Interviews; Motion picture producers and directors -- United States -- Interviews; Authors
Places
Texas -- In motion pictures
- Accession 2015-107
  - College Papers: Untitled Work, "Blue and White," "Cable Car," "Philosophy of Life," and "Bible Story" (Box 2102, Folder 1)
  - Dallas Observer Stories: Untitled Drafts for publication for the Dallas Observer (Box 2102, Folder 2)
  - Politics: Resume and Application for Public Information Officer (Box 2102, Folder 3)
  - Sketching Texas Women PSAs (Box 2102, Folder 4)
    Contents
    Biographical sketches of notable women such as Jane Wilkinson Long, EBJ Commencement Speech, Pearl S. Buck, Cynthia Ann Parker, Elizabeth Blackwell M.D., Sissy Farenthold, Mary McLeod Bethune, Lady Bird Johnson, Babe Zaharias, Emily Dickinson, Abigail Adams, Vilma Martinez, Mary Austin Holly, Clare Booth Luce, Martha Graham, Mother Jones, Lucy Stone, Calamity Jane, Oveta Culp Hobby, Marry Cassatt, Barbara Jordan, Louisa May Alcott, Mary Baker Eddy, Billie Holiday, Jane Adams, Francis Perkins, Mae West, Dolly Madison, Edna St. Vincent Millay, Anne Hutchinson, Marian Anderson, Margaret Mead, Lillian Russell, Aimee Simple McPherson, Amelia Earhart, Belle Star, Phyllis Wheatley, Rachel Carson, Isadora Duncan, Abigail Scott Duniway, Hetty Green, Nelly Bly, Shirley Chisolm, Henrietta Szold, Sacajawea.
  - VHS Tapes: Gary Cogill's Oscar Show, Women in Film Topaz Awards (Box 2102, Folder 5)
  - VHS Tapes: Lone Star Film and Television (Box 2102, Folder 6)
  - Photos: Photos of Sumner, Oliver Stone, Lonesome Dove Set, Brad Johnson, Walker Texas Ranger Cast of Chuck Norris, Sheree J. Wilson, Clarence Gilyard, Noble Willingham, and John Wayne (Box 2102, Folder 7)
  - Awards: Film Awards, 1978-2005 (Box 2102, Folder 8)
  - Awards: Veteran Feminist of America Award Program, 2010 (Box 2102, Folder 9)
  - Awards: Correspondence, 1974-1980 (Box 2102, Box 10)
  - Resumes, Job Applications, and Employment Information (Box 2102, Folder 11)
  - Portfolio of Jane Sumner's work and correspondence (2 folders) (Box 2102, Folder 12-13)
  - Magazine Stories (6 folders), 1975-2010
    - "Theater in Dallas" in Vision 1977, "The Park that Peter Built" in D Magazine 1977, and "The Incandescent Career of Margo Jones" D, The Magazine of Dallas 1975 (Box 2102, Folder 14)
    - "Portrait of the Revel as Donald Vogel" in D, The Magazine of Dallas undated, "Texas: The 'State' of Commercials" in On Location 1985, "Experimenting with Job Site Childcare" in Vision 1978 (Box 2102, Folder 15)
    - "All Access Pass" in Texas Highways 2010, "The Rosenthals of Aledo in Home Garden 1979, "Whither in Fair Park?" in Prime Time 1977 (Box 2102, Folder 16)
    - "Coping with Child Support" in Vision 1979, "Christians and Jews in Dallas" in Vision 1978, "Howard Mcgredy's Love Affair" in Dallas 1979, "Convention City" in Vision 1979 (Box 2102, Folder 17)
    - "Who's News" in New Women 1975, "The Emerald City on the Prairie" in Location 1991, "'13 East Comedy Comes to Texas" in The Hollywood Reporter 1990 (Box 2102, Folder 18)
    - "Another School System" in Vision 1979, "Karl Hoblitzelle: The Man Behind the Mansion" in Home Garden 1980 (Box 2102, Folder 19)
  - TV Picks and Pans: TV Show Reviews and Recommendation by Jane Sumner, 1993-1996 (Box 2102, Folder 20)
  - Interview Transcripts
    - Heath Ledger, Tom Copeland with photo, Robert Redford, Ned Blessing with call list, Woody Allen, and Tommy Lee Jones (Box 2102, Folder 21)
    - Richard Linklater, Gary Cartwright, Bill Moyers, Tim McCanlies, Tilda Swinton, Michael Caine (Box 2102, Folder 22)
    - Mickey Rourke, Tom Berenger, Ted Nugent, Sarah Bird, Patrick Swayze, Steve Irwin (Box 2102, Folder 23)
    - Kevin Spacey, Debbie Reynolds, Omar Sharif, Robert Duvall, Martin Sheen, Oliver Stone, Antonio Banderas, Sean Young (Box 2102, Folder 24)
    - Tom Hanks, Ed Harris, Kevin Bacon, Esther Williams, John Sayles, Danny Glover, Guillermo del Toro, Denzel Washington (Box 2102, Folder 25)
    - Patrick Swayze, Kris Kristofferson, Joan Collins, Bill Broyles, Warren Skaaren, Judith Ivy, Karl Malden, Michael Caine, Anne Rice, Diane Keaton, Ross Milloy, Chuck Norris (Box 2102, Folder 26)
    - Dennis Quaid, Dennis Franz, Shirley McLain, Ismail Merchant, Rabbi Bemporad, Bud Shrake, Father Taliaferro, John Grisham (Box 2102, Folder 27)
    - Brad Johnson, Mitzi Gaynor, Suzanne Finstad, Marcia Gay Harden, Kirk Douglas, Jack Warden, Donald Petric, Patsy Swayze (Box 2105, Folder 1)
    - Peter Weller, Danny Aiello, Stephen B. Ambrose, Will Taylor, Pat O'Connor, Selena and Edward James Olmos, Edna Buchanan, Mary Martin, Fay Wray (Box 2105, Folder 2)
    - Katie Oslin, Larry Clark, George Burns, Jason Patric, Eleanor Bergstein, Geena Davis, Sylvia Komatsu, Frank Muller, Nelson Runger, Sally Daring, Barbara Rosenblatt, William Hootkins (Box 2105, Folder 3)
    - Ali McGraw, Tony Danza, Tim Roth, Randy Quaid, Brian Dennehey, John Sayles, Kathy Bates, Mike Van Diem, Jim Brown, Cameron Diaz, Oliver Stone, Chuck Norris, Errol Morris, Sonia Braga, Jeremy Brett (Box 2105, Folder 4)
    - Jason Alexander, Steve Jaracho, Ross Milloy, Peter Fonda, Janine Turner, James Lee Burke, Maria Riva, Maury Povich, Peter Mayle, Raul Julia (Box 2105, Folder 5)
    - Lou Diamond Phillips, John Bodham, Charlton Heston (Box 2105, Folder 6)
    - Haley Joel Osment, Michael Jackson, Gary Cartwright, Deborah Laake, Eric Valli, Peggi Taylor (Box 2105, Folder 7)
  - Oversized Materials
    - Politics: Newspaper editorials written by Jane Sumner, 1976-1982 (Box 2103, Folder 1)
    - Awards: Achievement Award for Women in Film, Special Recognition Award from the City of Dallas, Veteran Feminists of America, Flowers Memorial Award, 2000, 2010, undated (Box 2103, Folder 2)
    - Awards: Correspondence, 1975-1992 (Box 2103, Folder 3)
    - Women for Change (Feminist Newspaper-Edited): Collection of Newspapers with articles by Jane Sumner (2 folders), 1970-1975 (Box 2103, Folder 4-5)
    - Obituaries written by Jane Sumner, 1993-1997 (Box 2103, Folder 6)
    - Film Reviews Written by Jane Sumner, 1987-2015 (Box 2103, Folder 7)
    - Reviews of TV Shows and Television Networks by Jane Sumner, 1990-1994 (Box 2103, Folder 8)
    - News articles by Jane Sumner regarding historic homes in Austin, including some on LBJ and Ladybird Johnson's homes, 2009-2012 (Box 2103, Folder 9)
    - Film Festival Stories: News articles on film criticism, The Dallas Film Festival, and film production by Jane Sumner's, 1986-2014 (Box 2103, Folder 10)
    - TV Movie Picks and Pans: News articles on TV and movie reviews by Jane Sumner in The Austin American Statesman and The Dallas Morning News, 1986-2011 (Box 2103, Folder 11)
  - Interview Tapes
    139 Microcassette interviews. Side A and Side B labels in quotation marks reflect Sumner's original labels. Also included are older audio cassettes (numbers 140-160)
    - 1. A: "Matt McConaughey"/B: "ED TV" (Box 2104, Item 1)
    - 2. A: "Teresa Wright"/B: "Pech" (Box 2104, Item 2)
    - 3. A: Christopher "Gordon"/B: "Jonathan Demme" (Box 2104, Item 3)
    - 4. A: "Stokes Hackman"/B: "Joseph M. Bride" (Box 2104, Item 4)
    - 5. A: "Harry Thompson"/B: "Harry Thompson" (Box 2104, Item 5)
    - 6. A: "MTM" Mary Tyler Moore/ B: "Mary Tyler Moore" (Box 2104, Item 6)
    - 7. A: "Will Taylor"/B: "John Sayles" (Box 2104, Item 7)
    - 8. A: "Tilda" Swinton/B: "Joe Mantegna" (Box 2104, Item 8)
    - 9. A: "Sissy" Spacek/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 9)
    - 10. A: "Alamo"/B: Stephen "Tobolowsky" (Box 2104, Item 10)
    - 11. A: "Frank"/B: "Tom Copeland" (Box 2104, Item 11)
    - 12. A: "Bruce Beresford"/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 12)
    - 13. A: "Tim McCanlies"/B: "Tim" McCanlies (Box 2104, Item 13)
    - 14. A: "Evan Adams"/B: Tommy "Lee" Jones (Box 2104, Item 14)
    - 15. A: "Bill Broyles"/ "Carwash" (Box 2104, Item 15)
    - 16. A: Tom "Berenger"/ "RR" (Box 2104, Item 16)
    - 17. A: Charlton "Heston"/ B: "Lilly" (Box 2104, Item 17)
    - 18. A: "Barney"/ "W. Wittliff" William Wittliff (Box 2104, Item 18)
    - 19. A: "Auto Focus"/B: "Debbie R." Debbie Reynolds (Box 2104, Item 19)
    - 20. A: Meryl "Streep"/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 20)
    - 21. A: "Fred Barzyck"/B: Bill "Wittliff" (Box 2104, Item 21)
    - 22. A: Robert "Duvall"/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 22)
    - 23. A: "Isabella Rosellini"/B: "Frank Thomas" (Box 2104, Item 23)
    - 24. A: "Fred Barzyk"/B: Bill "Wittliff" (Box 2104, Item 24)
    - 25. A: Robert "Duvall"/B: _____ (Box 2104, Item 25)
    - 26. A: "Isabella Rossellini"/ B: "Frank Thomas" (Box 2104, Item 26)
    - 27. A: "HAAS"/B: "Eric Roberts" (Box 2104, Item 27)
    - 28. A: "Gov. Ann Richards"/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 28)
    - 29. A: "Steve Irwin"/ B: Ian "McGregor" (Box 2104, Item 29)
    - 30. A: "Garry Shandling"/B: "Garry Barry" (Box 2104, Item 30)
    - 31. A: "Boroski"/B: "Russell Crow" (Box 2104, Item 31)
    - 32. A: "Ron Howard"/ B: Tom "Hanks" (Box 2104, Item 32)
    - 33. A: "Star"/B: "John Lee Hancock" (Box 2104, Item 33)
    - 34. A: "Anne Rapp"/B: "Keiko" (Box 2104, Item 34)
    - 35. A: "Control Room"/B: Richard "Linklater" (Box 2104, Item 35)
    - 36. A: "Tommy Lee" Jones/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 36)
    - 37. A: "Robert Redford"/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 37)
    - 38. A: "BBT"/B: "Tommy Lee Jones" (Box 2104, Item 38)
    - 39. A: Bill "Moyers"/B: Bill "Moyers" (Box 2104, Item 39)
    - 40. A: "Buzz Bissinger"/B: "Tim" (Box 2104, Item 40)
    - 41. A: "Maya Angelou"/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 41)
    - 42. A: "Rodrigo":/B: "Star Wars Chewy" (Box 2104, Item 42)
    - 43. A: "M. Corenblith" Michael Corenblith/B: Michael "Corenblith" (Box 2104, Item 43)
    - 44. A: Robert "Duvall"/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 44)
    - 45. A: Hector "Babenco"/B: Hector "Babenco" (Box 2104, Item 45)
    - 46. A: "Paul Shrader"/B: "Ross" (Box 2104, Item 46)
    - 47. A: "Auto Focus"/ B: "Vanessa Martinez" (Box 2104, Item 47)
    - 48. A: "Ned Blessing"/B: "Ned" Blessing (Box 2104, Item 48)
    - 49. A: "Emily Watson"/B: "Jim Caviezel" (Box 2104, Item 49)
    - 50. A: Christopher "McQuarrie"/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 50)
    - 51. A: "Danny Glover"/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 51)
    - 52. A: Peter "Bogdanovich"/B: "Tory Windle" (Box 2104, Item 52)
    - 53. A: "Cyd Charisse"/B: "Cynthia" (Box 2104, Item 53)
    - 54. A: Matthew "Damon"/ B: Stephen "Ambrose" (Box 2104, Item 54)
    - 55. A: "Antonio Banderas"/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 55)
    - 56. A: "Platt"/B: "Platt" (Box 2104, Item 56)
    - 57. A: "Tommy Lee" Jones/B: "Shirley MCL" MacLaine (Box 2104, Item 57)
    - 58. A: "Matthew McConaughey"/B: "Richard" (Box 2104, Item 58)
    - 59. A: "Roberts"/B: "Bill Wittliff" (Box 2104, Item 59)
    - 60. A: "Jason"/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 60)
    - 61. A: Benicio "del Toro"/B: "Tom Berenger" (Box 2104, Item 61)
    - 62. A: "Sean"/B: "Robert Drew" (Box 2104, Item 62)
    - 63. A: Barry "Levinson"/B: "Barry Levinson" (Box 2104, Item 63)
    - 64. A: "Thom"/B: "John Hannah" (Box 2104, Item 64)
    - 65. A: "Robin Tunney"/B: "Hartley" (Box 2104, Item 65)
    - 66. A: "Selena"/B: "Selena Set" (Box 2104, Item 66)
    - 67. A: "Tim McGraw"/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 67)
    - 68. A: "Shirley Barrett"/B: Tommy Lee "Jones" (Box 2104, Item 68)
    - 69. A: "Hugh Grant"/B: "Hugh" Grant (Box 2104, Item 69)
    - 70. A: "Jon Voight"/B: "Jon Voight" (Box 2104, Item 70)
    - 71. A: "Tim McCanlies"/B: "Tim" McCanlies (Box 2104, Item 71)
    - 72. A: Ian "McGregor"/B: John "Sayles" (Box 2104, Item 72)
    - 73. A: "Haley Joel Osment"/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 73)
    - 74. A: "G. Oldman" Garry Oldman/B: "I-LD" (Box 2104, Item 74)
    - 75. A: Bill "Paxton": /B_____ (Box 2104, Item 75)
    - 76. A: "Foote"/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 76)
    - 77. A: "Sonora Locke"/B: "Irma Hall" (Box 2104, Item 77)
    - 78. A: "Barry Levinson"/B: "FNL BBT" (Box 2104, Item 78)
    - 79. A: Leonardo "DiCaprio"/B: Debbie "Reynolds" (Box 2104, Item 79)
    - 80. A: Chuck "Norris"/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 80)
    - 81. A: Ken Loach/B: "H. Long" Howie Long (Box 2104, Item 81)
    - 82. A: "Chavez"/B: "Peter Berg" (Box 2104, Item 82)
    - 83. A: Edward James "Olmos"/B: Al Moovari (Box 2104, Item 83)
    - 84. A: "Heath Ledger"/B: "Butler" (Box 2104, Item 84)
    - 85. A: Ray "Liotta"/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 85)
    - 86. A: "Rodrigo"/B: Stephen "Frears" (Box 2104, Item 86)
    - 87. A: "AFC"/B: "Diane Keaton" (Box 2104, Item 87)
    - 88. A: Norman "Jewison"/B: Illegible (Box 2104, Item 88)
    - 89. A: "Travis Stacy"/B: "Chewie/Star Wars" (Box 2104, Item 89)
    - 90. A: Peter "Mullan"/B: "Luke Wilson" (Box 2104, Item 90)
    - 91. A: "Geo. Burns" George Burns/B: George "Burns" (Box 2104, Item 91)
    - 92. A: "K. Malden" Karl Malden/B: Karl "Malden" (Box 2104, Item 92)
    - 93. A: "Eric Valli"/B: "Marie Bon Maysles" (Box 2104, Item 93)
    - 94. A: "Walker"/B: "Cross" (Box 2104, Item 94)
    - 95. A: "Andie McDowell"/B: Antonio "Banderas" (Box 2104, Item 95)
    - 96. A: "Stecker/B: "Himalaya" (Box 2104, Item 96)
    - 97. A: Robert "Duvall"/B: "Wes" Anderson (Box 2104, Item 97)
    - 98. A: "Gael Garcia"/B: Illegible (Box 2104, Item 98)
    - 99. A: Matthew "Damon/B: Stephen "Ambrose" (Box 2104, Item 99)
    - 100. A:_____/B: "M. D. Fox" (Box 2104, Item 100)
    - 101. A: "Mike Judge"/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 101)
    - 102. A: "Tom Schatz"/B: "UT" (Box 2104, Item 102)
    - 103. A: "Hampton Francher"/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 103)
    - 104. A: "Elark"/B: Richard "Linklater" (Box 2104, Item 104)
    - 105. A: "Anne" Lamott/B: "Anne Lamott" (Box 2104, Item 105)
    - 106. A: "Brian Grazer"/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 106)
    - 107. A: "Patrick Wilson"/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 107)
    - 108. A: "Patrick Swayze"/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 108)
    - 109. A: "Esther Williams"/B: Dennis "Quaid" (Box 2104, Item 109)
    - 110. A: "Maysles"/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 110)
    - 111. A: "Reynolds"/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 111)
    - 112. A: "M. Caine" Michael Caine/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 112)
    - 113. A: _____/B: "Paul Peter" (Box 2104, Item 113)
    - 114. A: _____/B: Richard "Linklater" (Box 2104, Item 114)
    - 115. A: "Paul Sen"/B: "Paul Sen" (Box 2104, Item 115)
    - 116. A: Dennis "Quaid"/B: illegible (Box 2104, Item 116)
    - 117. A: "Steve Wilson"/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 117)
    - 118. A: Edward James "Olmos"/B: "C. Stevens" Cat Stevens (Box 2104, Item 118)
    - 119. A: Illegible /B: "Alamo" (Box 2104, Item 119)
    - 120. A: Peter "Wier"/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 120)
    - 121. A: "Masterson"/B: "Marx" (Box 2104, Item 121)
    - 122. A: Jacqueline "Lovell"/B: "Ind. Author" (Box 2104, Item 122)
    - 123. A: "Bill Broyles"/B: Dennis "Quaid" (Box 2104, Item 123)
    - 124. A: "Elizabeth Pena"/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 124)
    - 125. A: "Hayde"/B: "Gov. Ann Richards" (Box 2104, Item 125)
    - 126. A: "R. Witherspoon" Reece Witherspoon/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 126)
    - 127. A: Illegible/B: "T. H. Bacon" (Box 2104, Item 127)
    - 128. A: Charleston "Heston"/B: _____ (Box 2104, Item 128)
    - 129. A: Dennis "Quaid"/B: "Hudlin" (Box 2104, Item 129)
    - 130. A: "Debbie Reynolds"/B:_____ (Box 2104, Item 130)
    - 131. A: Tom "Hanks/B: "Nick Stahl" (Box 2104, Item 131)
    - 132. A: Paul "Hogan"/B: "Paul Hogan" (Box 2104, Item 132)
    - 133. A: "Leander Kennedy"/B: "Leander Kennedy" (Box 2104, Item 133)
    - 134. A: "Star Wars Chewie"/B: "Tom" Hanks (Box 2104, Item 134)
    - 135. A: "Malena" Alterio/B: "Ti Wright" (Box 2104, Item 135)
    - 136. A: "Boettinger"/B: "Boettinger" (Box 2104, Item 136)
    - 137. A:_____/B: "Randy Fritz" (Box 2104, Item 137)
    - 138. A: "Hume Cronyn"/B: "Tx Jus" (Box 2104, Item 138)
    - 139. A: Steven "Tobolowskey"/B: "S. Tobolowskey" (Box 2104, Item 139)
    - 140. A: "Beschloss"/ B: "Beschloss" (Box 2104, Item 140)
    - 141. A: "Shirley" MacLaine/ B: "Shirley MacLaine" (Box 2104, Item 141)
    - 142. A: "Martin, Mary"/ B: "RJ" (Box 2104, Item 142)
    - 143. A: A. A. "Taliaferro 10-25"/B: "A. A. Taliaferro 10-25" (Box 2104, Item 143)
    - 144. A: "Avery/James"/ B: "Lou Diamond Phillips, December 7, 1987 (Box 2109, Item 144)
    - 145. A: "Debbie Reynolds"/ B: "Joan Benny Martin, April 1990 (Box 2109, Item 145)
    - 146. A: Bill "Moyers"/B: Bill "Moyers" (Box 2109, Item 146)
    - 147. A: "Allen Weintraub"/B: Gail "Bugliosi" (Box 2109, Item 147)
    - 148. A: "Danza/Sharif"/ B: "Humann (LPS)" (Box 2109, Item 148)
    - 149. A: "Korda 3-07-91"/ B: "Joan Collins", October 1991 (Box 2109, Item 149)
    - 150. A:_____/ B: "Sonia Braga" (Box 2109, Item 150)
    - 151. A: "Bill Engvall"/ B: "Bill" Engvall" (Box 2109, Item 151)
    - 152. A: "Ali McGraw"/ B: "Ali McGraw" (Box 2109, Item 152)
    - 153. A: "Oliver Stone"/B:_____ (Box 2109, Item 153)
    - 154. A: "Stone/Adams 5-06-91"/ B: "Oliver Stone", May 6, 1991 (Box 2109, Item 154)
    - 155. A: "Hopper"/B:_____ (Box 2109, Item 155)
    - 156. A: "G. Rogers"/B: "AA Taliaferro 10-29" (Box 2109, Item 156)
    - 157. A: "Fay Wray"/ B: "Geo Burns" (Box 2109, Item 157)
    - 158. A: "Rise Stevens 12-20-90"/ B:_____, March 7, 1991 (Box 2109, Item 158)
    - 159. A: "Oliver Stone 4-6-91"/ B: "Stone Cont'd", April 6, 1991 (Box 2109, Item 159)
    - 160. A: "Peggy Taylor"/ B: "Peggy" (Box 2109, Item 160)
  - Film/TV Outtakes Columns, 1984-1995
    - News articles covering various film and TV series, 1985-1997 (Box 2106, Folder 1)
    - News articles about Movies and TV series, including Tom Hanks, Sally Fields, Chuck Norris, 1985-1992 (Box 2106, Folder 2)
    - News articles covering Films and TV series including articles on Tim Roth, Stephen Fry, Kevin Costner, Ann Richards, Oliver Stone, 1984-1992 (Box 2106, Folder 3)
    - News articles covering movies and TV series including Lou Diamond Phillips, 1984-1992 (Box 2106, Folder 4)
    - News article covering films and TV series including Bill Wittliff, Chuck Norris, Tommy Lee Jones, Brad Johnson, Clint Eastwood, 1984-1993 (Box 2106, Folder 5)
    - News articles covering films and TV series including articles on Robert Redford, Steven Spielberg, Ethan Hawke, Brad Pitt, Willie Nelson, 1987-1992 (Box 2107, Folder 1)
    - News articles covering films and TV series including articles on Patrick Swayze, Robocop, Texas Chainsaw Massacre 2, 1984-1992 (Box 2107, Folder 2)
    - News articles covering films and TV series including articles on Lou Diamond Phillips, Don Henley, Project X, Dennis Hopper, Robert Duvall, Kenny Rogers, 1984-1986 (Box 2107, Folder 3)
  - Texas Film and TV Production: News Articles on Films and TV shows, Lonesome Dove, The Alamo, JFK, 1987-2004 (Box 2106, Folder 6)
  - Texas Film and TV Production: News Articles on Film and TV shows, The Ballad of the Sad Café, Texas Chainsaw Massacre 2, Robocop, 1987-2004 (Box 2106, Folder 7)
  - News Stories Misc: Newspapers articles on Theater Productions, Texas Parks and Gardening, and Vegetarian Restaurants by Jane Sumner in The Dallas Morning News, 1986-2006 (Box 2106, Folder 8)
  - TV-Related Stories: News Articles about TV Shows and Celebrities by Jane Sumner, 1989-1995 (Box 2106, Folder 9)
  - Audio book reviews by Jane Sumner, 1991-1996 (Box 2106, Folder 10)
  - Sunday Magazine Columns: Various stories in Scene Magazine by Jane Sumner, 1977-1983 (Box 2107, Folder 4)
  - Informer columns: Articles by Jane Sumner in Dallas Life Magazine, 1982-1985
    - 1982-1983 (Box 2107, Folder 5)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 2107, Box 6)
    - 1983-1985 (Box 2108, Folder 1)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 2108, Folder 2)
    - 1982-1984 (Box 2108, Folder 3-5)
  - Author Interviews: Interviews between Sumner and various authors published in The Austin-American Statesman and The Dallas Morning News, 1988-2015 (Box 2110, Folder 1)
    Includes interviews with Bill Wittliff, Gary Cartwright, Shirley Temple Black, Michael Caine, John Grisham, Bill Moyers, and Maya Angelou
  - Film Interviews: Interviews with various actors and directors about their films and careers
    - Tommy Lee Jones, Tom Copeland, Willie Nelson, Debbie Reynolds, Patrick Swayze, Bill Engvall, Lou Diamond Phillips, Jon Bodham, Chuck Norris, Martin Sheen James, Earl Jones, 1990-2015 (Box 2110, Folder 2)
    - Charlton Heston, A.A. Taliferro, Patrick Swayze, Diane Keaton, Shirley MacLaine, Jeff Bridges, and Jon Voight, 1985-2014 (Box 2110, Folder 3)
  - Book reviews written by Jane Sumner in The Austin- American Statesman and The Dallas Morning News, 1985-2015 (Box 2110, Folder 4)